[Script Info]
; Written for the vetus poeta tests
Title: UTF-16
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H64000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,40,40,40,1
Style: Top,Arial,54,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H64000000,0,1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,40,40,40,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:03.00,Default,,0,0,0,,The baker's oven is still warm.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.50,0:00:06.00,Default,,0,0,0,,Pistor pānem in furnō coquit.
